Guide to the Brooklyn Historical Society institutional records ARC.288
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 7: Curatorial Affairs and Collections, 1862-2020
  - Sub-series 7.13: Curatorial Department Files, 1977-2011, bulk 1984-2007
    - Zoning Codes, 1988 (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 207, Folder 11-12)
      Contains the outgoing correspondence of Anne Marie Barba, Acting Registrar and Curatorial Assistant (ca. 1988-1990).
    - BHS Openings [Photographs], 1989 (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - City Seminar [Meeting Notes], 1989 (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - Coney Island, 1989 (Box 207, Folder 15)
    - Industry, 1989 (Box 207, Folder 16)
    - The Long Island Historical Society: After a Century, Change [Report], 1989 (Box 207, Folder 17)
    - Mobil Oil Archives, circa 1989 (Box 207, Folder 18)
    - Waterfront, circa 1989 (Box 207, Folder 19)
    - Andros Patent Letters [Photocopies], circa 1990s (Box 207, Folder 20)
    - BHS Indian Life Catalog [Prints and Negatives], circa 1990s (Box 207, Folder 21)
    - Brooklyn -- Background, circa 1990s (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Catalogue Card Mechanical, circa 1990s (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Educational Programming [Research Notes], circa 1990s (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Fulton Landing [Floor Plans], circa 1990s (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Malcolm Mackay [Articles], circa 1990s (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Exhibit Negatives, circa 1990s (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Photography, circa 1990s (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - "Object Temporarily Removed" Labels, circa 1990s (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - Possible Proposal Photos, circa 1990s (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Slide Sorting Notes, circa 1990s (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - General Press, 1976-1990 (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - The Houdini Exhibit [Proposal], 1983-1990 (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - Appraisers, 1984-1990 (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - [American Association of Museums Accreditation], 1987-1990 (Box 208, Folder 14-15)
    - Rejected Donations, 1987-1990 (Box 208, Folder 16)
    - Brooklyn Organizations, 1990 (Box 208, Folder 17)
    - Prints [Research], 1990 (Box 208, Folder 18)
    - Teen Tokyo Proposal, 1990 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - [Memos], 1989-1991 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - 1991 Tax Law (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Categories, 1991 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Funding for Museum Projects, 1991 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Inter Museum Storage Facilities, 1991 (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Legal Problems of Museum Administration [Conference], 1991 (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Off-site Storage Possibilities, 1991 (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Reception for Black Leaders, 1991 (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Empire State Building [Potential Exhibit], 1990-1992 (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - Exhibit Builder [Magazine], 1992 (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - [Project Updates], 1992 (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - Possible Acquisitions, 1988-1993 (Box 209, Folder 13-15)
    - Exhibition Scheduling, 1991-1993 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Board Games -- Liman Collection, circa 1992-1993 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - AAM Annual Meeting [Minutes], 1993 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Exhibit Suggestions, Ideas from Visitors, 1993 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Journal of Urban History, 1993 (Box 210, Folder 5)
      Includes an interview with David Kahn about urban history at the Brooklyn Historical Society.
    - AAM Panel Presentation, 1993-1994 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Curatorial Fact Sheet, 1993-1994 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - AAM Annual Meeting Session Proposal, 1994 (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Awards for Museum Leadership Seminar, 1994 (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - Criteria for Good Exhibitions, 1994 (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - Potential Exhibit Ideas, 1994 (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - Rejected Donations, 1994 (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - Internal Meetings [Notes], 1992-1995 (Box 210, Folder 13)
    - Chief Curator -- General Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 210, Folder 14)
    - Chief Curator -- Notes, Letters, etc., 1993-1995 (Box 210, Folder 15)
    - Curatorial Staff Meetings [Notes], 1994-1995 (Box 210, Folder 16)
    - [Meeting Notes], 1994-1995 (Box 210, Folder 17)
    - Programming (Notes, Memos), 1994-1995 (Box 210, Folder 18)
    - Audience Research Questionnaire, 1995 (Box 210, Folder 19)
    - Entering Data on ARGUS [Instructions], 1995 (Box 210, Folder 20)
    - Past BHS Exhibit Reviews, 1995 (Box 210, Folder 21)
    - Wild Impressions Exhibit [The Adirondack Museum], 1995 (Box 210, Folder 22)
    - [Margo Williams Files], 1994-1996 (Box 211, Folder 1-2)
      Margo Williams was Curator of Collections from 1994 to 1996. These files contain correspondence, invoices, and documentation related to the relocation of collections off-site.
    - [Anne Grant Correspondence], 1995-1996 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - American Social History Project Workshop Materials, circa 1996 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Community Conversations, 1996 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Community Conversations Notes, 1996 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Curatorial Research Requests, 1996 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition Spaces, 1996 (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - MANY Workshop, 1996 (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Tasks, 1996 (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Curatorial Monthly Reports, 1995 August - 1997 March (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Echo [Newsletters], 1995, 1997 (Box 211, Folder 12)
      Includes five issues of Echo, the Chapman Historical Museum's newsletter.
    - Barnum Museum, 1997 (Box 211, Folder 13)
    - Collection Notes and History, 1997 (Box 211, Folder 14)
    - Ellis Island Interviews [Book Excerpt], 1997 (Box 211, Folder 15)
    - Museums Kunde [German Publication], 1997 (Box 211, Folder 16)
      Includes an article about community-related exhibitions at BHS.
    - Whither the Dodgers, 1997 (Box 211, Folder 17)
    - African Burial Ground, 1996-1998 (Box 211, Folder 18)
    - Weeksville, 1997-1998 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Arts and History Orgs, 1998 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Bluestone, 1998 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Commemorative Buttons, 1998 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Forest City Ratner, 1998 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Gerald Stern, 1998 (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - The Greater New York Centennial Celebration, 1998 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Heritage Trail Proposal, 1998 (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Lott House Photos, circa 1998 (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Museum Theatre [Research], 1998 (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Price Lists, 1998 (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - Prospect Park Photos, circa 1998 (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - Sheepshead Bay [Research], 1998 (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - [Curatorial Slides], circa 1980-1999 (Box 666)
      Subjects include: 00 Numbers, 4th Floor Storage 1989, 4th Floor Storage 1991, African Americans in Brooklyn, Artifacts, BHS Building Photos, BHS Front, BHS History, BHS Interior, BHS Lobby, BHS Publications, BHS Staff, Brooklyn Bridge and Other Architecture, Brooklyn Interiors, Brooklyn Neighborhoods, Brooklyn's History Museum, Brownsville
    - [Curatorial Slides], circa 1980-1999 (Box 667)
      Subjects include: Busts, Cemeteries, Death and Dying, Color Charts, Coney Island, Conservation of Eagle, Conservation of Works of Art on Paper, Conservation of Works of Art on Paper – Unknown Object Numbers, Crown Heights, Curatorial Office, Daily Eagle Building. Drawings – Shellens, Education, Exhibit Photos, Flag Storage, Giglio, Honeymooners, Jewish Life, John Mackie Falconer Paintings, Lecture – Cast-Iron and Cottage Living, LIHS Building, LIHS Events, LIHS Proposal and Architectural Drawings, Martha Cooper Photography
    - [Curatorial Slides], circa 1980-1999 (Box 668)
      Subjects include: Miscellaneous Collection Photography, Miscellaneous Slides Found in Old Curatorial File Boxes, Navy Yard, NEA Paper and Paintings Grant 1994, Objects Not in BHS Collection, Paintings / Works of Art on Paper, Paintings Storage (Conservation Grant), Paintings Storage (Unknown Date), Paintings Storage 1985, Paintings – Detail for Conservation, Paintings –Pre IMS Conservation Grant 1992, Pierrepont House Drawings, Portraits, Print Storage, Problem Slides
    - [Curatorial Slides], circa 1980-1999 (Box 669)
      Subjects include: Promenading, Public Programs, Shellens – 3/11/88 (Pre-Construction), Shellens Renovation 1988, Sunset Park 11/90 (Chinese Community), Sunset Park 4/29/91 (Chinese Community), Walking Tours, Walt Whitman, West Indian Carnival, Williamsburg
    - Brooklyn Eagle Statue [Photos], circa 1989-1999 (Box 212, Folder 14)
    - Environment [Newsletters], 1994-1999 (Box 212, Folder 15)
      Includes five issues of the New York State Environment, published by the Department of Environmental Conservation, and one issue of Environmental Impact, the newsletter of Park Slope Action for the Environment.
    - Steeplechase Films, 1996-1999 (Box 212, Folder 16)
    - ARGUS Manifest, 1997-1999 (Box 213, Folder 1-8)
      Contains a printout of the museum's ARGUS collections database
    - BHS Press, 1998-1999 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn Works, 1998-1999 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Collections Management and Care Summary, 1998-1999 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota Historical Society, 1998-1999 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Voices of Brooklyn, 1998-1999 (Box 214, Folder 5-6)
      Voices of Brooklyn was a 40-minute performance that told the story of 19th-century Brooklyn through songs, poems, dances, newspaper diaries, photos, and other primary sources. This production was created to celebrate the 100th anniversary of the consolidation of Greater New York.
    - [Voices of Brooklyn Brochure], 1998 (Box 505, Folder 18)
      Removed from Box 214, Folder 5-6: Voices of Brooklyn, 1998-1999.
    - [Voices of Brooklyn Posters], 1998 (Box 506, Folder 6)
    - Curator of Collections Report, circa 1999 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - AAM Annual Meeting, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Cocoa Port [Photos and Negatives], 1999 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Domino Workers [Photos and Negatives], 1999 October (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Guide to the Pierrepont Papers, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - Joe Schwartz, Temporary Exhibit Possibility, circa 1999 (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - Montague St. Arts Festival, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 13)
    - Museum Assessment Program, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 14)
    - NYSCA Program Guidelines, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 15)
    - Photographers, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 16)
    - Schomburg, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 17)
    - Tom Flagg, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 18)
    - MetroTech, circa 1998-2000 (Box 214, Folder 19)
      Contains one zip disk.
    - Curator of Collections Goals, 1999-2000 (Box 214, Folder 20)
    - Place Matters, 1999-2000 (Box 214, Folder 21)
    - Program Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 214, Folder 22)
    - [Building Research], circa 1990s-2000s (Box 214, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Photos, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Architecture Slides, circa 2000s (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Exhibit Planning Sheet, circa 2000s (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Ferber Gardner Report, circa 2000s (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - General Brooklyn History, circa 2000s (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Map Photography, circa 2000s (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Margaret Weekes, circa 2000s (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Archives Binder, circa 2000 (Box 215, Folder 8-10)
      Includes lists of archival materials curatorial staff consulted while working off-site.
    - Bridge Street Church, circa 2000 (Box 215, Folder 11)
    - The Evergreens, circa 2000 (Box 215, Folder 12)
    - Letters of Recommendation for BHS, 2000 (Box 215, Folder 13)
    - Minnesota Historical Society Visit [Photos], circa 2000 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - PS 131, circa 2000 (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - Architecture of Segregation, 2000 (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Bernie Springsteel, 2000 (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - Brooklyn History Discovery Center, 2000 (Box 216, Folder 5-6)
    - Empire Stores [Photos and Negatives], 2000 March (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Five Black Arts, 2000 (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - Future Programs and Projects, 2000 (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - Gil Hodges, 2000 (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - Gotham Center, 2000 (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - Leonard Gaskin, 2000 (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - Lost Museum Project, 2000 (Box 216, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Photos, 2000 (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - Old Stone House, 2000 (Box 216, Folder 15)
    - Tobacco Warehouse, 2000 (Box 216, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Dare, Harborside, Waterfront Museum [Photos and Negatives], 2000 June (Box 216, Folder 17)
    - Williamsburg, 2000 (Box 216, Folder 18)
    - Henry Kirke Brown Plaster, 1996, 2000-2001 (Box 216, Folder 19)
    - [Correspondence], 1996-2001 (Box 216, Folder 20)
    - Museum Theatre, Lynne Conner, 1999-2001 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Neighborhood History Guide Research, 1999-2001 (Box 217, Folder 2-3)
    - An American in Brooklyn, 2000-2001 (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Gotham Center, 2000-2001 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - BHS Marketing / Brochure, 2001 (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Bibliography of New York Writing, 2001 (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - Bridget Parris Studio, 2001 (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - Brooklyn Works, 2001 (Box 217, Folder 9)
    - Chicago Historical Society, Facing History and Ourselves, 2001 (Box 217, Folder 10)
    - The Colonial Revival in America [Conference], 2001 (Box 217, Folder 11)
    - Exhibit Ideas, 2001 (Box 217, Folder 12)
    - The Long Island Museum, 2001 February (Box 217, Folder 13)
    - Medgar Evers College [Meeting Notes], 2001 (Box 217, Folder 14)
    - Museum Theatre, French Canadian "Strike", 2001 (Box 217, Folder 15)
    - Proposed Temporary Exhibitions, 2001 (Box 217, Folder 16)
    - Urban Studies [Proposal for Young Curators], 2001 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - Website, 2001 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - [Separation and Transfer Forms], circa 1988-2002 (Box 218, Folder 3-11)
    - World Trade Center -- Collections / Info, 2001-2002 (Box 218, Folder 12)
    - World Trade Center -- Response, 2001-2002 (Box 218, Folder 13)
    - Charles Wallert, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 14)
    - Dorothy Duckett Joseph, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 15)
    - Exhibit Lighting, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 16)
    - Exhibit Schedule, 2002 (Box 218, Folder 17)
    - Housing -- Bushwick [Research], 2002 (Box 218, Folder 18)
    - International Tile Company, 2002 (Box 219, Folder 1-3)
    - New Deal Conference Notes, 2002 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - Program Committee [Notes], 2002 (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - Samuel Anderson, 2002 (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - Collection Highlights, circa 2000-2003 (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - Weeksville, 2000-2003 (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - 128 Pierrepont Research, 2001-2003 (Box 219, Folder 9-11)
    - 128 Pierrepont Research, 2001-2003 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Bread and Roses, 2002-2003 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - Dutch Visitors Thank You Letter, 2003 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - John Jay H.S. Project [Notes], 2003 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - Historic Structure Report -- 128 Pierrepont St, 2003 (Box 220, Folder 5-6)
    - MCNY U.N Exhibit [Notes], 2003 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - Museum and Millwork Division [Project Bid], 2003 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - Brooklyn Artists, 1998-2004 (Box 220, Folder 9-11)
    - Brooklyn Artists, 1998-2004 (Box 221, Folder 1-3)
    - Shellens Move, 1999-2004 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - Building Tour Scripts, circa 2004 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - BHS Photos, 2002-2004 (Box 221, Folder 6-7)
      Folder 6 contains 20 optical discs and folder 7 contains 21 optical discs.
    - [Cynthia Sanford Correspondence], 2002-2004 (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - Jewish Heritage Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - Front Burner Exhibits, 2004 (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - Heritage Health Index, 2004 (Box 221, Folder 11)
    - [Meeting Notes], 2004 (Box 221, Folder 12)
    - Sewing Machine Shops [Photographs], 2004 (Box 221, Folder 13)
    - [Deslyn Downes] Bulletin Board, circa 2003-2005 (Box 221, Folder 14)
    - Curatorial Department Files [Box List], 2004-2005 (Box 221, Folder 15)
    - Herbert Luey, 2005 (Box 221, Folder 16)
    - Making Art Work [Brooklyn Arts Council Event Flyer], 2005 (Box 221, Folder 17)
    - Bennett Ryder Family [Research], 2006 (Box 221, Folder 18)
    - Dinanda Nooney [Research], 2006 (Box 221, Folder 19)
    - Exhibit Planning, circa 2006 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Lutherans in Brooklyn [Article], circa 2006 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Methodist Episcopal Churches [Research], 2006 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Proteus Gowanus, 2006 (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - J.M. Falconer [Research], 2006-2007 (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - BHS Building Research, 2007 (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - Col. Joshua Sands [Research], 2007 (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - Currently on View, 2007 (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - Exhibition Laboratory, 2007 (Box 222, Folder 9)
    - Partition Street, 2007 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Saint Francis Xavier Church, 2007 (Box 222, Folder 11)
      Contains 1 DVD.
    - City Tech, 2008 (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - Exhibitions and Programs [Meeting Notes], 2008 (Box 222, Folder 13)
    - BHS Advertisements, 2008-2009 (Box 222, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition Schedule, 2008-2009 (Box 222, Folder 15)
    - Code of Ethics for Curators, 2009 (Box 222, Folder 16)
    - Suba Drawings and Barber Poles [Leaflet], 2009 (Box 222, Folder 17)
    - Brooklyn Navy Yard, 2007-2010 (Box 222, Folder 18)
    - Press [Newspaper Clippings], 2007-2010 (Box 222, Folder 19)
    - Jersey Prison Ships, circa 2010s (Box 222, Folder 20)
    - The Social History of Flatbush, circa 2010s (Box 222, Folder 21-22)
    - Exhibitions and Programs, 2008-2011 (Box 222, Folder 23)
  - Sub-series 7.14: Deaccessioning Program, 1980-1998, bulk 1991-1998
    Materials in this sub-series are arranged chronologically. Lot files appear at the end.
    Under the direction of Head Librarian Irene Tichenor (1988-1996), the library undertook a deaccessioning project in the early 1990s to refine its collection. Tichenor began identifying and preparing out-of-scope materials for removal between 1991 and 1995. In December 1995, she hired Bob Heman as Collections Manager to oversee this task.
    Sub-series 7.14: Deaccessioning Program includes plans, lists, notes, bids, and correspondence related to the deaccessioning program conducted by library staff from 1991 to 1998. The bulk of this material consists of Lot Files, which contain bibliographic information for titles identified as out-of-scope and potential candidates for deaccession. Lot subjects are detailed at the file level.
    - Newspapers, 1980, 1992-1993 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Deaccessioning Plan, 1989, 1991 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Candidates for Deaccessioning, circa 1989-1991 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - Deaccession Records Pre-1995 (Box 223, Folder 4)
      The bulk of this file contains bids and correspondence related to the newspapers up for sale.
    - Files Labeled Candidates for Deaccessioning (Pre-12/95), 1995 (Box 223, Folder 5-6)
    - Library Committee Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 223, Folder 7)
    - Deaccession Note File, 1996 (Box 223, Folder 8)
    - Deaccessioning Periodicals (Box 223, Folder 9)
    - Museum Deaccessions, 1996 (Box 223, Folder 10)
    - Book Dealers [Contact Cards], circa 1996 (Box 223, Folder 11)
    - Book Flow for Items to be Kept, circa 1996 (Box 223, Folder 12)
    - [Antiquarian Bookseller's Association of America Membership Directory], 1996-1997 (Box 223, Folder 13)
    - Income, 1996-1997 (Box 223, Folder 14)
    - Lists Relating to Deaccession, 1996-1997 (Box 223, Folder 15)
    - Bid Charts, 1996-1998 (Folder Flat File)
    - [Bid Correspondence], 1996-1998 (Box 223, Folder 16)
    - [Bid Correspondence], 1996-1998 (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - Bob Heman's Files, 1996-1998 (Box 224, Folder 2)
    - High Bids [Correspondence], 1996-1998 (Box 224, Folder 3-5)
    - Lots Kept in Process or No Bidders, 1996-1998 (Box 224, Folder 6-7)
    - Sculpture List, 1996-1998 (Box 224, Folder 8)
    - Deaccessioned Materials, 1996-1999 (Box 224, Folder 9)
    - Background, 1998 (Box 224, Folder 10)
    - [Correspondence], 1998 (Box 224, Folder 11)
    - Lot-1 [Books Offered for Sale], circa 1991-1992 (Box 224, Folder 12)
    - Lot-1 [Books Offered for Sale], circa 1991-1992 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Lot-1 [Pull Cards Printout], circa 1991-1992 (Box 225, Folder 2-6)
    - Lot-2 [Books Offered for Sale], circa 1991-1992 (Box 225, Folder 7)
    - Lot-2 [Pull Cards Printout], circa 1991-1992 (Box 225, Folder 8-10)
    - Lot-3 [Author and Subjects Lists], circa 1992 (Box 225, Folder 11)
    - Lot-3 [Books Offered for Sale], 1992 (Box 225, Folder 12)
    - Lot-3 [Pull Cards Printout], circa 1992 (Box 225, Folder 13)
    - Lot-4 [Books Offered for Sale], 1992-1993 (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - Lot-5 [Author and Subject Lists], circa 1992-1993 (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - Lot-5 [Books Offered for Sale], circa 1992-1993 (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - Lot-5 [Pull Cards Printout], circa 1992-1993 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - [Lot 96-1 -- Lot 96-4], 1996 (Box 226, Folder 5)
      Lot Subjects: George Washington, Civil War/Lincoln Newspapers, College, Institutional Serials
    - [Lot 96-5 -- Lot 96-6], 1996 (Box 226, Folder 6)
      Lot Subjects: Virginia, North Carolina
    - [Lot 96-7 -- Lot 96-12], 1996 (Box 226, Folder 7)
      Lot Subjects: Delaware, Camden Society, 19th Century Periodicals, Fillmore Inscription, The West
    - [Lot 96-13 -- Lot 96-21], 1996 (Box 226, Folder 8)
      Lot Subjects: Encyclopedias, American History Sets, Continental Congress, Constitution, Texas, Louisiana, Oklahoma, Arkansas
    - [Lot 96-22 -- Lot 96-28], 1996 (Box 227, Folder 1)
      Lot Subjects: Italy, Agriculture, Hunting, Antiques Magazine, Poetry, Virginia and North Carolina Periodicals
    - [Lot 96-29 -- Lot 96-35], 1996 (Box 227, Folder 2)
      Lot Subjects: Ireland, Dore Bible, Kansas, Missouri, Nebraska, Iowa, Literary Journals, Great Britain, Philadelphia Directories, Newspapers
    - [Lot 96-36 -- Lot 96-39], 1996 (Box 227, Folder 3)
      Lot Subjects: Medicine, Lincoln Assassination, Lincoln Pamphlet, The South
    - [Lot 97-40 -- Lot 97-49], 1997 (Box 227, Folder 4)
      Lot Subjects: Pennsylvania Gazette, Illustrated Periodicals (Harpers Weekly, etc.), New York Times (Civil War Years), New York Historical Society, European Folios, Special American Imprints, Special English Items, New England Historical and Genealogical Register, British Periodicals
    - [Lot 97-50], 1997 (Box 227, Folder 5)
      Lot Subjects: British Local History
    - [Lot 97-51 -- Lot 97-59], 1997 (Box 227, Folder 6)
      Lot Subjects: Mid-Week Pictorial, Scientific American, Benjamin Franklin, The Dial, Law, New York Governors, New York City Directories, U.S. Government, Foreign Language Titles
    - [Lot 97-60], 1997 (Box 227, Folder 7)
      Lot Subjects: Maryland and Washington, D.C.
    - [Lot 97-61 -- Lot 97-66], 1997 (Box 228, Folder 1)
      Lot Subjects: Facsimiles Relating to America, Thomas Paine, Genealogy and History Serials, Misc. New York State Serials, Noah Webster, Ohio, Kentucky, West Virginia, Indiana
    - [Lot 97-67 -- Lot 97-71], 1997 (Box 228, Folder 2)
      Lot Subjects: New York State Assembly and Senate, Tennyson's Elaine, Massachusetts Related, Misc. Newspapers
    - [Lot 97-72 -- Lot 97-77], 1997 (Box 228, Folder 3)
      Lot Subjects: Reference Books, European and World History, American Historical Association, Natural History, Geographic Survey, Census
    - [Lot 98-78 -- Lot 98-80], 1998 (Box 228, Folder 4)
      Lot Subjects: Confederate Imprints, British and Foreign Almanacs, Europe,
    - [Lot 98-81], 1998 (Box 228, Folder 5)
      Lot Subjects: Art
    - [Lot 98-82 -- Lot 98-84], 1998 (Box 228, Folder 6)
      Lot Subjects: Large Illustrated Titles, Rolled Maps, Wisconsin, Illinois, Michigan,
    - [Lot 98-86 -- Lot 98-90], 1998 (Box 228, Folder 7)
      Lot Subjects: Arabian Knights, Daniel Webster, Americana, Universities, Textbooks
    - [Lot 98-92 -- Lot 98-98], 1998 (Box 228, Folder 8)